[Music]
to support the fundamentals of
subscription and to make that business
Central sales conversation easier we
have added a new subscription billing
feature set it gives you the tools to
manage subscriptions ensuring contracts
are properly documented manage with the
correct term for the services billing
frequency renewals terms and termination
conditions allowing you to run the
recurring billing process in a way that
can be adapted to your billing Rhythm
and get subscription build on time of
course it also allows you to recognize
subscription Revenue that follows your
reporting Cadence in
finance subscription billing enables you
to run usage based billing for your
subscriptions by importing quantities
and prices for the recurring billing
process in a. CSV file or a custom
API subscription billing is part of the
essential business Central license
[Applause]